<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Valuations on Running on R</title>
    <link>/categories/valuations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Valuations on Running on R</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/valuations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dropbox Valuation - Quick N&#39; Clean</title>
      <link>/2019/09/dbx-q3-quicknclean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/09/dbx-q3-quicknclean/</guid>
      <description>Dropbox Valuation - Quick N’ Clean Click any link in the list below to jump to topic
 What is Dropbox What Sets Dropbox Apart Digging into the financials Relative &amp;amp; Intrinsic Valuations Is Dropbox Really a Buy  Dropbox’s shares have fallen -27.6% from its July high of $26.20, which was under the recent February high of $26.49 as of 09/06/2019. It’s also -56.4% under the ATH of $43.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce Q3 Update</title>
      <link>/2019/01/salesforce-q3-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/salesforce-q3-update/</guid>
      <description>#Salesforce Q3 Update - Updated model from previous post, click here to read previous Salesforce post - Management raised top and bottom line forecasts for FY19 guidance - Management gave more details on FY20 &amp;amp; FY22 goals and confirmed forecasts - Near bulletproof business model during economic slowdown - Key risks to management goals - Recommendation and price targets

Salesforce (CRM) carried on with its tradition of beating expectations and raising future forecasts in its most recent quarterly results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce, Inc. - Are Expanding Margins Enough to Buy?</title>
      <link>/2018/11/salesforce-enough-to-buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/11/salesforce-enough-to-buy/</guid>
      <description>#Salesforce, Inc. - Leader in the growing CRM market - Modestly expanding margins - Monetizing existing customer base

###Customer Relationship Management Pioneer Whenever Customer Relationship Management is the topic of discussion, it’s almost impossible not to see Salesforce mentioned as the pioneer and leader. Salesforce currently has the largest market share of the CRM segment and is expected to continue gaining market share. Before we dig in to Salesforce specifically, let’s explore what exactly CRM is and the growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>