<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investment on Jagger with Swagger</title>
    <link>/categories/investment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investment on Jagger with Swagger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/investment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yield Curve Inversion - Marks End to Bull Market?</title>
      <link>/2018/12/yield-curve-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/yield-curve-fun/</guid>
      <description>Going, Going, Inverted!  Yield Curve inversions are typically a leading indicator for a recession Historic analysis on inversions for specific yields since 1990 Yield Curve over 5 different time frames since the start of 2018 Takeaway from recent inversions   Yield Curve Inversion I’ve always followed bank stocks ever since I first began investing almost 6 years ago. Once I learned the 10-year and 2-year treasury spread was a profit driver for the big banks, I began to track the daily fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce, Inc. - Are Expanding Margins Enough to Buy?</title>
      <link>/2018/11/salesforce-enough-to-buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/11/salesforce-enough-to-buy/</guid>
      <description>Salesforce, Inc.  Leader in the growing CRM market Modestly expanding margins Monetizing existing customer base  Customer Relationship Management Pioneer Whenever Customer Relationship Management is the topic of discussion, it’s almost impossible not to see Salesforce mentioned as the pioneer and leader. Salesforce currently has the largest market share of the CRM segment and is expected to continue gaining market share. Before we dig in to Salesforce specifically, let’s explore what exactly CRM is and the growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>