<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Running on R</title>
    <link>/categories/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Running on R</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using MySQL with R</title>
      <link>/2019/05/mysql-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/05/mysql-r/</guid>
      <description>Using MySQL with R  Benefits of a Relational Database Connecting to MySQL and reading + writing data from R Simple analysis using the tables from MySQL  If you’re an R programmer, then you’ve probably crashed your R session a few times when trying to read datasets of over 2GB+. It can get a little frustrating when all you want to do is harness the true power behind R through building statistical models on these large datasets, and your session crashes with a window stating “R SESSION ABORTED”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sentiment Analysis on Earnings Call</title>
      <link>/2019/04/sentiment-analysis-conf-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/04/sentiment-analysis-conf-call/</guid>
      <description>Conference Call Text Mining and Sentiment Analysis  Executives are very careful with the language they use during a conference call Using sentiment scores to validate future / long-term goals Checking for negation words that can affect score Key takeaways from this analysis  Do you ever notice when our president sends out a tweet and the markets spike/drop almost instantly, or within seconds of news going public, millions of shares are being traded based off what was said or done?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>