<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Algo on Running on R</title>
    <link>/tags/algo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Algo on Running on R</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/algo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AlpacaforR</title>
      <link>/2019/04/alpaca-for-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/04/alpaca-for-r/</guid>
      <description>#AlpacaforR
 What is Alpaca and AlpacaforR Some Example Functions Implementing the Earnings Strategy Some Bonus Example Functions - Live Account Users Learn more about Alpaca and AlpacaforR Github  
After writing my recent post Scaling a Simple Earnings Strategy to the NASDAQ Exchange, I started to research how I could implement that earnings strategy into a live brokerage account directly from R. Most of us have heard of Quantopian or other backtesting services, but things can get complicated quickly once you search for a way to implement a live strategy using R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaling a Simple Earnings Strategy to the NASDAQ Exchange</title>
      <link>/2019/03/backtest-simple-earnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/03/backtest-simple-earnings/</guid>
      <description>#Pure Earnings Play
 Getting the data and writing the function Top sectors and stocks from results Beautiful plots to visualize the results Quick review How to improve the simple strategy  
You often hear two things when watching or reading financial news. One is earnings season, and another is quantitative trading. Most people prefer to manage their own money and pick the companies their most familiar with when making trading decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>